const quizQuestions = [
    { //1
        question: "This franchise played in Cleveland, Los Angeles, and St. Louis. Which team is this?",
        choices: ["Rams", "Chargers", "Browns", "Vikings"],
        correctAnswer: "Rams"
    },
    { //2
        question: "The 2008 Indianapolis Colts franchise joined the NFL in 1953 under which name?",
        choices: ["Indianapolis Colts", "Cleveland Colts", "Baltimore Colts", "New York Colts"],
        correctAnswer: "Baltimore Colts"
    },
    { //3
        question: "In what city did the Washington Redskins originally play?",
        choices: ["New York", "Los Angeles", "Tampa", "Boston"],
        correctAnswer: "Boston"
    },
    { //4
        question: "Which team was given the nickname The Ain'ts during the 1980 NFL season?",
        choices: ["New Orleans Saints", "Cincinnati Bengals", "Green Bay Packers", "Chicago Bears"],
        correctAnswer: "New Orleans Saints "
    },
    { //5
        question: "The Miami Dolphins had the first undefeated season in NFL history. In 1985, which undefeated team did they beat, to make sure their legacy remained?",
        choices: ["Buffalo Bills", "Chicago Bears", "Tennessee Titans", "Oakland Raiders"],
        correctAnswer: "Chicago Bears"
    },
    { //6
        question: "Which team was given the nickname America's Team in the 1979 NFL season?",
        choices: ['Houston Texans', "New York Giants", "New England Patriots", "Dallas Cowboys"],
        correctAnswer: "Dallas Cowboys"
    },
    { //7
        question: "Which team has lost five Super Bowls?",
        choices: ["Minnesota Vikings", "New England Patriots", "Buffalo Bills", "Kansas City Chiefs"],
        correctAnswer: "New England Patriots"
    },
    { //8
        question: "Which team was wide reciever Antonio Brown recently traded to, after spending 8 seasons with the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
        choices: ["Oakland Raiders", "Buffalo Bills", "New York Jets", "Los Angeles Chargers"],
        correctAnswer: "Oakland Raiders"
    },
    { //9
        question: "The longest field goal kick in NFL history, made by Matt Prater, was how many yards?",
        choices: ["55 yards", "61 yards", "64 yards", "59 yards"],
        correctAnswer: "64 yards"
    },
    { //10
        question: "What team was wide reciever Odell Beckham Jr traded to this offseason?",
        choices: ["New York Giants", "Cleveland Browns", "Cincinnati Bengals", "Denver Broncos"],
        correctAnswer: "Cleveland Browns"
    },
    { //11
        question: "Of the three Watt brothers, which one plays for the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
        choices: ["JJ Watt", "TJ Watt", "Derek Watt", "John Watt"],
        correctAnswer: "TJ Watt"
    },
    { //12
        question: "Which of the Manning brothers played for 18 seasons, winning two Super Bowls?",
        choices: ["Peyton Manning", "Eli Manning", "Cooper Manninng", "Archie Manning"],
        correctAnswer: "Peyton Manning"
    },
    { //13
        question: "How many Super Bowl wins do the Pittsburgh Steelers have?",
        choices: ["2", "4", "6", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6"
    },
    { //14
        question: "Where will the 2020 Super Bowl be played?",
        choices: ["MetLife Stadium", "Gillette Stadium", "Three Rivers Stadium", "Hard Rock Stadium"],
        correctAnswer: "Hard Rock Stadium"
    },
    { //15
        question: "What team plays at Lambeau Field?",
        choices: ["Green Bay Packers", "Philadelphia Eagles", "Washington Redskins", "Carolina Panthers"],
        correctAnswer: "Green Bay Packers"
    },
    { //16
        question: "What team plays at CenturyLink Field?",
        choices: ["Tampa Bay Buccaneers", "Seattle Seahawks", "Arizona Cardinals", "San Francisco 49ers"],
        correctAnswer: "Seattle Seahawks"
    },
    { //17
        question: "Where is the Pro Football Hall of Fame located?",
        choices: ["Springfield, MA ", "Washington, D.C.", "Columbus, OH", "Canton, OH"],
        correctAnswer: "Canton, OH"
    },
    { //18
        question: "Patrick Mahomes, the 2019 NFL MVP plays for what team?",
        choices: ["Miami Dolphins", "Kansas City Chiefs", "San Francisco 49ers", "Dallas Cowboys"],
        correctAnswer: "Kansas City Chiefs"
    },
    { //19
        question: "After a perfect 16-0 season, the New England Patriots lost Super Bowl 42 to what team?",
        choices: ["New York Giants", "New York Jets", "Detroit Lions", "Green Bay Packers"],
        correctAnswer: "New York Giants"
    },
    { //20
        question: "How many Super Bowl rings does Super Bowl MVP Drew Brees have?",
        choices: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
        correctAnswer: "One"
    },

];